{"test_questions": [[{"question": "\"If you don't keep quiet I shall shoot you\", he said to her in a calm voice.", "opta": "He warned her to shoot if she didn't keep quiet calmly.", "optb": "He said calmly that I shall shoot you if you don't be quiet.", "optc": "He warned her calmly that he would shoot her if she didn't keep quiet.", "optd": "Calmly he warned her that be quiet or else he will have to shoot her.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "I told him that he was not working hard.", "opta": "I said to him, \"You are not working hard.\"", "optb": "I told to him, \"You are not working hard.\"", "optc": "I said, \"You are not working hard.\"", "optd": "I said to him, \"He is not working hard.\"", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "His father ordered him to go to his room and study.", "opta": "His father said, \"Go to your room and study.\"", "optb": "His father said to him, \"Go and study in your room.\"", "optc": "His father shouted, \"Go right now to your study room\"", "optd": "His father said firmly, \"Go and study in your room.\"", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "He said to his father, \"Please increase my pocket-money.\"", "opta": "He told his father, \"Please increase the pocket-money\"", "optb": "He pleaded his father to please increase my pocket money.", "optc": "He requested his father to increase his pocket-money.", "optd": "He asked his father to increase his pocket-money.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She said that her brother was getting married.", "opta": "She said, \"Her brother is getting married.\"", "optb": "She told, \"Her brother is getting married.\"", "optc": "She said, \"My brother is getting married.\"", "optd": "She said, \"My brother was getting married.\"", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The boy said, \"Who dare call you a thief?\"", "opta": "The boy enquired who dared call him a thief.", "optb": "The boy asked who called him a thief.", "optc": "The boy told that who dared call him a thief.", "optd": "The boy wondered who dared call a thief.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She exclaimed with sorrow that was a very miserable plight.", "opta": "She said with sorrow, \"What a pity it is.\"", "optb": "She said, \"What a mystery it is.\"", "optc": "She said, \"What a miserable sight it is.\"", "optd": "She said, \"What a miserable plight it is.\"", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Dhruv said that he was sick and tired of working for that company.", "opta": "Dhruv said, \"I am sick and tired of working for this company.\"", "optb": "Dhruv said, \"He was tired of that company.\"", "optc": "Dhruv said to me, \"I am sick and tired of working for this company.\"", "optd": "Dhruv said, \"I will be tired of working for that company.\"", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "\"Are you alone, my son?\" asked a soft voice close behind me.", "opta": "A soft voice asked that what I was doing there alone.", "optb": "A soft voice said to me are you alone son.", "optc": "A soft voice from my back asked If I was alone.", "optd": "A soft voice behind me asked If I was alone.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She said to him, \"Why don't you go today?\"", "opta": "She asked him why he did not go that day.", "optb": "She said to him why he don't go that day.", "optc": "She asked him not to go that day.", "optd": "She asked him why he did not go today.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "He exclaimed with joy that India had won the Sahara Cup.", "opta": "He said, \"India has won the Sahara Cup\"", "optb": "He said, \"India won the Sahara Cup\"", "optc": "He said, \"How! India will win the Sahara Cup\"", "optd": "He said, \"Hurrah! India has won the Sahara Cup\"", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The little girl said to her mother, \"Did the sun rise in the East?\"", "opta": "The little girl said to her mother that the sun rose in the East.", "optb": "The little girl asked her mother if the sun rose in the East.", "optc": "The little girl said to her mother if the sun rises in the East.", "optd": "The little girl asked her mother if the sun is in the East.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The man said, \"No, I refused to confers guilt.\"", "opta": "The man emphatically refused to confers guilt.", "optb": "The man refused to confers his guilt.", "optc": "The man told that he did not confers guilt.", "optd": "The man was stubborn enough to confers guilt.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Nita ordered her servant to bring her cup of tea.", "opta": "Nita told her servant, \"Bring a cup of tea.\"", "optb": "Nita said, \"Bring me a cup of tea.\"", "optc": "Nita said to her servant, \"Bring me a cup of tea.\"", "optd": "Nita told her servant, \"Bring her that cup of tea.\"", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "My cousin said, \"My room-mate had snored throughout the night.\"", "opta": "my cousin said that her room-mate snored throughout the night.", "optb": "my cousin told me that her room-mate snored throughout the night.", "optc": "my cousin complained to me that her room-mate is snoring throughout the night.", "optd": "my cousin felt that her room-mate may be snoring throughout the night.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "\"Please don't go away\", she said.", "opta": "She said to please her and not go away.", "optb": "She told me to go away.", "optc": "She begged me not to go away.", "optd": "She begged that I not go away.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She said to her friend, \"I know where is everyone\"", "opta": "She told that she knew where was everyone.", "optb": "She told her friend that she knew where was everyone.", "optc": "She told her friend that she knew where is everyone.", "optd": "She told her friend that she knows where was everyone.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}